namespacestrategy.com 2014-04-23

# NameSpace - The Value of Brand Protection

Your privacy is important to NameSpace, Inc. (“NameSpace”, “we” or “us”). This Privacy Policy outlines the principles and practices that apply to information collected from end-users, whether directly or through network partners such as Internet Service Providers.

**The NameSpace Service:**   
NameSpace works with Internet Service Providers and other network partners to provide relevant direct navigation events when a user enters into the address bar a brand-based query that cannot be resolved by one of our partners. NameSpace navigates users only when entered queries clearly contain or reflect brand and trademark names belonging to our brand customers (merchants and advertisers) and partners.

**Collection of Personal Information:**   
NameSpace does not collect or capture any personally identifiable information. We may collect anonymous information related to use of the service, which may include origination IP address, queries, or the IP address to which a query is directed. NameSpace takes reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to, or disclosure of collected information. In no event will NameSpace use or sell information which relates to a user’s personally identifiable use of the Internet. 

**How NameSpace uses the information collected:**   
NameSpace uses collected information to assess and improve our existing services, develop new services, diagnose technical problems, and allocate the resources of our systems. 

**To whom NameSpace discloses information:**   
From time to time, NameSpace may disclose collected information: 

  * To a user’s Internet Service Provider. 
  * To organizations that perform services for or on behalf of NameSpace, which may include data processing, or to measure the use of our services. 
  * To protect ourselves against liability or prevent fraudulent activity; or where it is necessary to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit any damages that NameSpace may sustain, to effect a corporate transaction, in connection with the sale, merger, or other corporate reorganization of our company, where the information is transferred to the new controlling entity in the regular course of business.
  * Where the information is public.
  * To our insurers or to comply with a subpoena, warrant or court (or similar) order.
  * To a person who needs the information because of an emergency that threatens the life, health, or security of an identifiable person or group, or where necessary to collect monies owing to us.

**Children:**  
NameSpace services are not designed or intended for use by children under 13, although participating merchants on our site may offer children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you should use NameSpace only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Children under 13 may not submit any personally identifiable information to us, and if we discover that we have inadvertently gathered any such information from a child under 13, we will take appropriate steps to delete it.

**Third Party Advertising:**  
We work with third parties, including advertising companies, who may use cookies and clear gifs to collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Web site and other sites or are offered the opportunity to participate in an incentive. This information may be used to provide you with better shopping or savings opportunities through advertisements on this and other Web sites that you visit, or to conduct market research and website analysis. Users who visit a the website of a brand customer of NameSpace may receive cookies or gifs intended to help analyze their use of the merchant's site in relation to their satisfaction and use of that site.

**Participating Merchant Policies:**  
Online merchants, survey incentive vendors, and others who participate in NSG services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants, survey incentive vendors, and other third parties, we cannot be responsible for their actions. We recommend that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**Protective Measures for End-Users:**   
NameSpace will not, at any time, request credit card information, Member ID, login password, or national identification numbers. For more information about the practice known as "phishing," and to learn how to protect themselves in online transactions, users may want to visit the Federal Trade Commission at <http://www.ftc.gov/>. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**   
NameSpace may change or supplement this Privacy Policy from time to time. We may also undergo a change of ownership. NameSpace will post an appropriate notice of changes to the Privacy Policy and changes or ownership at [www.namespaceinc.com](http://www.namespaceinc.com/). Privacy Policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date NameSpace posts the revised Privacy Policy at [www.namespaceinc.com](http://www.namespaceinc.com/), as well as to existing information held by NameSpace.
